Good luck, Tanaka Taro!
じゃあ 頑張れよ！ 田中太郎君
As a member of The Dollars, I'll hold onto this.
これは ダラーズの一員として オレが預かる
You're acting pretty tough despite Harima Mika being gone.
張間美香がいなくなったのに でかい顔してるみたいじゃない？
How does this thing die?
こいつ どうやったら死ぬんだ？
Did you hear? There's been another
incident involving The Slasher in Ikebukuro.
知ってるだろ？ 池袋でまた斬り裂き魔が出たって
Then I'll have to make a war break out that only I can cause.
オレにしかできない戦を起こすまでだ そうだろ？
Right?
ふっ切れた！
I've had it!
Welcome, Welcome!
イラッシャ～イ イラッシャイ
It's Russia Sushi!
「ロシアズシ」ヨ～ うまいヨ～ 安いヨ～
It's good!
It's cheap!
Eat sushi!
スシ 食いネ～
The Slasher...
斬り裂き魔… また出た
...struck again!
How many people does that make?
何人目？
This is the scene where yesterday,
protests against The Slasher took place.
ここが 昨夜 斬り裂き魔が犯行を行った現場です
Six months ago, a large-scale gathering
occurred suddenly in downtown Ikebukuro.
半年前 池袋の繁華街で突如発生した大規模な集会
And The Slasher incidents began at about the same time, didn't they?
斬り裂き魔が現れはじめたのもちょうど このころなんですよね
Also, amongst teenagers, something called the "headless rider" has—
また 池袋の若者たちの間で首なしライダーなる存在が…
America has already made contact with the headless rider and wants—
アメリカはすでに首なしライダーと接触し
そのテクノロジーを…
The Slasher?!
斬り裂き魔？
The headless rider...
首なしライダー
I'm so scared!
怖～い
Something is born and something disappears every day in this town.
街では日々何かが生まれ 消えていく
No way!
But...
It's good to eat.
Even so, nothing happens. Nothing changes.
それでも 何も起きない
Really?
何も変わらない
The Dollars?
That's...
それが 彼女の日常
Her everyday life.
Everything about our love is fake.
オレたちの愛は何もかも偽物だ
Yet it's stronger than the real thing.
でも 本物よりも強いんです
I love the wound on your neck.
オレはお前の首の傷を愛する
How is that wound connected to true love?
その傷を通して 本物の愛へとつながるんだ
I love you, Seiji.
私は誠二さんを愛しています
I love everything about you with all my heart!
誠二さんのすべてを全力で愛します
I get jealous every time I see them.
何度見ても うらやましい
Then just don't watch them.
なら 見なきゃいいのに
If you see a beautiful girl, you look at her—and talk to her.
きれいな女の子がいたら見る！ そして声を掛ける！
That's what's been embedded in our DNA as part of Team Boys, right?
それがＤＮＡに刻まれた 我らチーム男子の宿命だろ！
Don't lump me in with you...
一緒にしないでほしいな
However, don't worry.
だが 安心してくれ
My body may belong to everyone, but my heart is yours alone, Anri.
オレの体はみんなのものだが
心は杏里だけのものだから
Eh?!
I've always thought, "Just how can Anri be so erotically cute?"
オレはいつも思うわけだ
杏里はどうして そんなにエロかわいいのかって
E-Eh?!
She's not erotic.
いや エロはない エロはないよ 正臣
She's not erotic, Masaomi!
I sheee.
なるほど エロはともかく
Eroticism aside, you do admit that she's cute.
かわいいのは認めるわけだ
Eh?
Uh, well...
いや それは…
Oh? Then you're saying she's not cute...?
ほ～う ならば杏里はかわいくないと？
Sh-Sh-She's cute!
か… かわいいよ！ かわいいけどさ！ うっ…
She's cute, but...!
I see. So, you acknowledge that she's cute.
そうか かわいいのは認めるか
Yet I also acknowledge that she's erotic.
だが オレは杏里のエロさも認めている
In other words, acknowledging Anri's eroticism
means I better understand and love her more deeply.
つまり オレはお前よりエロの分 杏里を深く理解し 愛しているわけだ
This battle finally...ends with my victory!
よって この勝負 オレの勝ち！
Why do you get to decide everything all by yourself?!
何？ そのオレ様判定
You lose, Mikado!
帝人の負け！
Six months ago, a small disturbance occurred.
半年前 ちょっとした騒ぎが起こった
Everyone was talking about it all over town, and even in school.
街でも学校でも しばらくはその話題で持ちきりだった
However, it didn't have anything to do with her.
しかし 彼女には関係ない 興味もない
She's not even interested in it.
Are you okay?
大丈夫？
Uh, yeah.
あっ… うん ありがとう
Thank you.
Nothing happens.
何も起きない
Nothing changes.
何も変わらない
That's...her everyday life.
それが彼女の日常
Huh?
Man, I'm glad I had some points saved up.
Hurry it up.
早くしろ
ポイント たまっててよかったっす～
What're you going to do about the poster?
ゆまっち あのポスター どうすんの？
She's in a hurry.
(静雄)飛ばしてんなぁ…
What's with her? She's riding around even more than before.
なんかよぉ 最近 前にも増して 堂々と走ってねぇか？
Yeah, she is.
そうっすねぇ
I'd want her to be a little sneakier about it, wouldn't you?
ああいう存在はもうちょっとこっそりしていてほしいんっすよねぇ
It'd be perfect if we were the only ones
to know, like finding out a rich girl's secret.
「お嬢様の秘密」みたいに
私たちだけが知ってるくらいがちょうどいいのにね
Like "Nogizaka Haruka's Secret."
「乃木坂春香の秘密」っすね！
You two...
お前らなぁ～
Don't be like that.
まあ そう言うな きっといろいろあんだろうよ
They've got their own problems.
And her, too.
あいつにも
Hey, look!
おい 見ろよ！ 首なしライダーだ！
It's the headless rider!
This is Celty Sturluson's everyday life.
これがセルティ?ストゥルルソンの日常
It was...something she was used to.
いつもの慣れたことだった
People who're drawn into the abnormal tend to panic.
非日常に引きずり込まれた人間はパニックを起こす
In that instant, she easily escapes.
その隙に悠々と脱出する
That was how Celty Sturluson did things.
それがセルティ?ストゥルルソンのやり方だった
But...
だが…
I've always thought...
いつも思ってた オレたちはお前みたいなのが出てくる漫画や映画の中で いつだってかませ犬だ
"In the manga or movies in which someone like
you would appear, we're always made to play the fool."
Whenever the superpower-wielding protagonist enters, we're always
face down in pools of blood, dramatizing how strong his opponent will be.
超能力者の主人公様が現れたときにゃ いつだって血だまりの中に倒れていて
相手の強さを演出していた
That's fine...
それは いいんだ
Since it means we're considered that strong.
それだけ オレたちが強い存在と思われてる ってことだからな
It's something you can't help during production.
演出として しようがないことだ
But there's one thing I'd like to say.
だけど ひと言言いたいと思っていたんだよ
If a real monster, evil psychic, cyborg, or ninja were to appear...
本当に怪物とか 悪のサイキッカーとか 人造人間とか 忍者が現れたら
I'd have one thing...
ひと言だけ… ひと言だけなんだよ オレが言いたいのは
...one thing to say:
Don't underestimate traffic cops, you monster.
交機をなめるなよ… 化け物
I'll say it again.
もう一度言うぞ
Don't underestimate traffic cops, you monster look-alike.
化け物風情が交機をなめるな
Celty!
セルティ！ おかえり…
Welcome—
What? What's wrong?
何？ どうしたの？
Being embraced by you is an honor deeper
than the deepest oceans and wider than the sky.
君に抱きしめられるなんて 僕にとってはまさしく山高水長の誉れ
Uh, I guess that doesn't quite work.
いや 使い方微妙に間違えているけど…
Hey, you're shaking...
ちょっと… なんか震えてるよ
Really, what's wrong?
どうしたのさ？ 本当に セルティ？
Celty...
I-I-It was so scary!
こ… 怖かった 怖かったぞ 新羅！
It was so scary, Shinra!
Th-Th-The police nowadays are monsters!
さ… 最近の警察は 化け物だ！
The police?
警察って…
A pack of ten or eleven white and
silver vehicles chased me down and...
１０台近い白バイやパトカーが
まるで 一つの生き物みたいに私のことを追い詰めてきて…
So, you're saying a huge group of people on white bikes came after you to challenge your authority?
そういえば 君に対抗するために
よそからすごい白バイ隊員が来たとか
I have heard there's a problem officer named Kuzuhara Kinnosuke, who often causes accidents by over-pursuing offenders.
確か原金之助って
相手を追い込みすぎて よく事故らせる問題警官らしいけど…
I was so scared.
怖かった… 本当に怖かった
I really was.
I was too conceited.
慢心してた
From now on I'll live modestly, so please forgive me.
これからはつつましく生きていくから 許してください ごめんなさい…
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Who're you apologizing to?
誰に謝ってるのさ？
Showing vulnerability isn't like you, Celty.
そんな弱気なセルティ セルティらしくないよ
Although, if you were to show it to me in bed—
僕に弱さを見せるのはベッドの中だけで…
Don't say such embarrassing things at a time like this.
こんな流れで恥ずかしいことを言うな
Okay. That's fine.
そう… それで いい…
Anyway, I'm sorry about that, but...
そ… それでさぁ そんなところを悪いんだけど
Could you go meet someone for me?
ちょっと 人を迎えに行ってもらえないかな？
No, it's not a job.
いや 仕事じゃないんだ…
うん… 帰って来たんだよ 父さん
My...father's come back.
Jeez...
まったく タクシーにでも乗ってくればいいものを…
He could just catch a taxi...
He was pretty meddlesome back then, but...
昔から私にちょっかいを出してくるヤツだったが…
Hey, hey, hey!
What's that?
なんだ？ おら…
Say something!
なんか言ってみろよ
He's pretty white.
白いなぁ
Too white...
Oh, man...
まさか…
What's with you, geezer?
なんだぁ？ このおっさん
He's wearing a pretty cool outfit.
いかした格好してますよねぇ 法螺田さん！
Right, Horada?
You three.
君たち 東京は空気が汚い そうは思わんかね？
Don't you think the air in Tokyo is dirty?
Huh?!
はあっ!?
It seems like that dirty face of yours would normally
serve as excellent protection, but in this filthy air...
もっとも その汚い顔は立派な保護色となっているようだ
この汚れきった空気の中ではな
Hey, it looks like this geezer's full of himself!
おい このおっさん どっかわいてるっぽいぜ
Meh, it doesn't matter.
まあ いいんじゃないっすか？
It looks like the time has come to teach you about the power of adults.
どうやら大人の力を思い知らせてやるときが来たようだな
Under the Juvenile Act, you can kill people and still be protected.
貴様らは自分たちが少年法で守られて 好き勝手に人を殺すことができる
Or I assume that's what you think.
そう思ってるだろうがね
Remember this!
覚えておきたまえ
When you try to kill someone, you'd better
be prepared to possibly get killed by—
人を殺そうとするときには その相手に殺される覚悟を…
I guess you are full of yourself, geezer.
やっぱわいてんだろ おっさん
I'm over twenty years old!
オレはもう二十歳過ぎてんだよ！
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ちたまえ 本気で痛いし
This really hurts, and I can't run away because you're stepping on my feet..
靴踏まれてるから逃げられん…
I'm being finger-stabbed!
指刺さる 指刺さる
あ痛っ あ痛っ…
What're you doing, Celty?!
何をしてるんだね セルティ君！
Huh?!
Help me now!
早く私を助けたまえ！
Huh...?
I really don't want to help him...
助けたくないなぁ…
Don't you realize that the reason I acted so bold with
these people is because I felt safe when I saw you?
私が強気に対応したのは君の姿が見えて安心したからだということに 気づかないのかね？
あっ 法螺田さん こいつ 黒バイクっすよ！
Horada, this's the black biker.
What?! Are you serious, Higa?!
何？ マジか 比賀！
Yeah, I saw her on TV.
マジっす オレ テレビで見たっす
Weren't you at that Dollars thing six months ago?
おめぇも半年前のダラーズの集会にいたそうじゃねぇか
Man, everybody's tryin' to act tough here on our island.
ったく どいつも こいつも オレたちのシマで でけぇ面しやがって
What's up?! Say something!
どうした？ なんか言ってみろよ
Huh?!
Huuuuuuuuh?!
Huh?
What is this?!
なんだ こりゃあ!?
Yep, that was the right response.
うん これが正しい反応だよな
Great, it's not broken.
よかった 壊れてない
It's so important to me because I got it from Shinra.
新羅がくれた大事なものだから
Did you see that?
見たか これが大人の力なのだ！
This is the power of adults!
Nope, I'll never like him.
やっぱり… 好きになれない
Is there any meaning to using these?
これ 本当に意味あるの？
Just what kind of rules do you use?
だから 一体どういうルールよ
Russia Sushi, Russia Sushi!
「ロシアズシ」 「ロシアズシ」ヨ～
Boss...
社長～
Oh, Izaya!
オオ～ 臨也！
Yo. You're working as hard as ever, I see.
よう 相変わらずよく働くなぁ
You've been coming to Ikebukuro a lot lately.
最近 池袋 よく来るネ
If you're here, you should stop by the restaurant.
せっかくだから 店 寄るヨ
I just opened up the canned goods this morning.
今朝カンヅメ開けたばっか～り ネタは新鮮ヨ
The ingredients are so fresh!
Sorry, but I'm busy with some stuff.
悪いね これでもいろいろ忙しくって
Maybe some other time.
そのうちまた寄らしてもらうよ
ヘイ！
"You can't hide an awl in a bag."
"Don't talk about ropes in a house where someone hanged himself," was it?
Alright, let's say what we like about
Anri to show who understands her better.
じゃあ オレと帝人 どっちが杏里を理解しているか
杏里のいいとこを言いっこしよう！
I'll go first. Her eroticism!
まずオレ… エロいとこ
You're going to start with that?!
いきなり そこ？
Stop talking about erotic stuff.
エロから離れようよ エロから
Those who laugh at eroticism will be reduced to tears by it.
エロを笑う者はエロに泣くのだぞ
That doesn't make any sense.
いや 意味分かんないし
This was her first experience being friends with boys.
男子と仲よくなるのは初めての経験だった
Anyway, Mikado, what do you like about Anri?
Well, I...uhh...
Well, to be exact, she'd probably never been friends with anyone before.
いや 正確には 誰とも仲がよかったことなどなかったのかもしれない
"There's nothing good about Anri...poo poo." Is that it?
I didn't say that!
そんなこと言ってないじゃん！
Then tell me. Right now! Quickly!
じゃあ言え すぐ言え さっさと言え！
いや…
In the past, she was only around to make Harima Mika look good.
かつて 彼女は張間美香という少女の引き立て役でしかなかった
Three, two, one!
But that was fine.
でも それでよかった
That was her place.
そこが彼女の居場所だった
However...
しかし… その場所を失った今
Now that she's lost that place, she's been unable to find a new one.
彼女は自分の立ち位置を見つけられずにいた
Okay, in order to prove how erotically
cute you are, Anri, let's all go pick up girls!
よし！ 杏里のエロかわいさを証明するために
これから三人でナンパに行こう！
What kind of logic is that?!
何？ その理屈
By "pick up," you mean...
ナ… ナンパって…
It'll be fine.
大丈夫 杏里はいわば「女の子もいるからついていっても大丈夫だろう」と
Anri's the trap to make them think, "Oh, there's a girl here, so it'll be okay to go off with them," so she doesn't have to do anything.
安心させるための罠だから
何もしなくても オーケーだ！
W-W-Wait a minute, Masaomi!
ちょっと待ってよ 正臣！
Alright, let's go! Everyone, follow me!
よし 行くぞ！
者ども ついてこい！
Get set, and...bang!
レッツラド～ン！
Let's do this!
行っくぞ～！
K-Kida...
き… 紀田君？
Masaomi!
正臣～！
Do you really think it's okay?
本当によかったのかな…
It's fine. He'd just be hitting on girls by himself anyway.
いいって どうせ一人でもナンパはするんだから
Honestly...
まったく…
What a pain.
世話が焼ける
I have to make a big scene about it since you're so shy.
おくて君にはこれくらいのハンデあげないとね
I'm such an incendiary man.
オレって 憎い男だぜ
ったくよ…
楽しんじゃおう
Umm...
あの…
She did notice that the two boys loved her.
二人の少年が自分に好意を抱いていることには気づいていた しかし…
However...
Uh, the sunset's really pretty, isn't it?
夕焼け きれいだね
Eh?
Uh, but there are some weird clouds over there...
でも あっちに変な雲が…
It might rain later, so be careful.
あとで雨が降るかもしれないから気をつけようね
You're right.
そうですね
Umm...
あの…
Eh?!
えっ 何!?
What?
This is it for me.
私 ここで…
Eh?
Well, see you tomorrow.
それじゃあ また 明日
Uh, yeah, see you tomorrow...
また 明日
The sunset was a bad idea.
はぁ…夕焼けはないよなぁ 夕焼けは
She probably couldn't answer, no matter who confessed to her...
たぶん今どちらかに告白されても何も答えられない
Because she still liked Harima Mika.
彼女は今でも張間美香のことが好きだった
The two of them are so similar...
同じくらい二人のことも
That the girl still doesn't understand the difference between friendship and love.
彼女はまだ友愛と恋愛の違いは分かっていない
What do Harima Mika, Ryugamine Mikado, and Kida Masaomi mean to her?
彼女にとって張間美香は…
竜ヶ峰帝人は… 紀田正臣は…
Can we get you to change your answer?
どうしてもダメですか？
We really do need you...
オレたちやっぱりあんたがいないと…
I've told you, I have nothing to do with this anymore.
だから言ってるだろ
オレはもう関係ねぇ
This isn't where I belong.
ここはオレの居場所じゃねぇんだ
I don't plan on coming back...to your side.
戻る気はねぇんだよ こっち側にはな
Really?! That's so funny!
超ウケる～
There've been a lot more people wearing yellow around town recently.
最近 町に黄色い人たちが増えてきましたね
Yellow?
黄色？
That's so true. They stand out more than
The Dollars because you can tell who they are.
ほんとですよね－ はっきり姿が見える分 ダラーズより目立ってますよー
Oh, are you talking about The Yellow Scarves?
ああ 黄巾賊ですか？
You know them, Setton?
セットンさんもご存じですか？
Yes, well...
ええ まあ…
They've been around for a while.
昔からいますねえ あの連中
And The Yellow Scarves are...
黄巾族って……
They're an old gang in Ikebukuro.
昔 池袋にあったチームです
They disappeared after getting into a fight with another gang.
他のチームとの抗争がきっかけで姿を消したんですけどね～
Ahh, I've heard that story before.
ああ その話なら聞いたことあります
Does this mean they're back together?
復活したってことですか？
Ikebukuro's all up in arms again.
池袋も物騒になってきましたね
Seriously. And the police are scary, too.
ほんとに… 警察も怖いですし
I'm serious.
いや 本気で！ 警察をなめないでください
Don't underestimate the police.
The police?
警察？
Aw, she fell down.
うわっ 転んでるよ～
How lame.
ダサッ！
All you did was kick her a bit.
軽くけっただけなのに
You're such an idiot.
ほんと鈍くさいよね
That's cuz she's a parasite.
やっぱ ギョウ虫だから
What's with the face?!
なんだよ？その面は
It doesn't look like The Slasher Case will be solved anytime soon.
切り裂き魔の事件も解決しそうにありませんしねぇ
Speaking of that, have you heard?
そういえば知ってます？
There's a rumor that The Slasher is in The Dollars.
切り裂き魔の正体はダラーズだってうわさ
There are rumors that the headless rider is, too.
首なしライダーっていううわさもあるそうですよ？
Eh?! Who's spreading that?!
え！？誰がそんなことを！
I doubt it's true.
それはないと思いますよ？
All joking aside...
冗談はさておき…
You really should be careful of The Yellow Scarves.
黄巾族には本気で気をつけたほうがいいよ
自分たちがいない間に 勢力を伸ばしたダラーズのことを快く思ってない連中もいるからね
Some of them don't take too kindly to the fact we expanded our influence while they weren't around.
Is that so...
そうなんですか…
Alright, I'll be careful.
分かりました 気をつけます
Honestly...
ったくよ
You sell yourself to Ryugamine and Kida after Harima, and then Nasujima on top of that?!
張間の次は竜ヶ峰と紀田にこび売って
おまけに那須島かよ
How many people are you going to sell your body to until you're satisfied?
何人に体売れば気が済むんだよ この援交女！
You whore!
All you can do is live off of someone else, you parasite.
誰かに寄生しなきゃ生きていけねぇくせしてさ ギョウ虫！
Parasite!
ギョウ虫
ギョウ虫！
She wondered, "Maybe what those girls are saying really is true."
少女は思っていた 彼女たちの言っていることは本当だと
She used to be dependent upon Harima Mika.
自分は張間美香に依存していた
And she might still be...
そして たぶん今も…
What're you bein' all quiet for?!
何 黙ってんだよ！
Say something!
なんとか言えよ！
What? Parasites don't have mouths?!
ギョウ虫には口もねぇのかよ！
Now she might be dependent upon those two boys...
今も 二人の少年に依存しているのかもしれない
...trying to find her place amongst them.
彼らの中に自分の居場所を見つけようと…
You reek, parasite!
臭ぇんだよ ギョウ虫！
学校来てんじゃねぇよ！
Don't ever come to school!
It's your fault I've lost two boyfriends!
こっちはあんたのせいで二人も彼氏やられてんだからね
What're you spacing out for?!
何ぼけっとしてんだ！ああ？
She'd gone about protecting her heart and body in this way.
こうやって彼女は自分の身を心を守り続けてきた
Nothing happens.
何も起きない
Nothing changes.
何も変わらない
That's her everyday life.
それが 彼女の日常
Your house is nearby, isn't it? You should let us in. We'll search it for you!
あんたの部屋この近くなんだろ？
ちょっと上がらせなよ
Hurry up and take us there!
ガサ入れタイムしてやっからよ
You better do it if you wanna make up for what you've done!
ほら さっさと案内しな
Saika has entered the chat room.
It's here!!
Ah...
Huh?
I cut.
I want to cut.
I'm the one who wants to cut you!
I cut.
I want to cut.
Wrong.
Is this the person who was spamming any
message board related to Ikebukuro six months ago?
Wrong.
Weak, wrong,
Can't, control
You haven't banned this person yet?
Weak, wrong,
Can't, control
Desire, is, want
I did!
It doesn't work, no matter how many times I do it!
Desire, is, want
Love, not enough, love
Oh, I see.
Want, love, people
I banned the IP address, but they just use a different host and come back.
More, strong, love, want
Ah, you mean a proxy?
Desire, I, mother, mother
Hmm, it doesn't look like it's a proxy...
More, strong, love, want
Desire, I, mother, mother
Wow, that's scary.
[Mother]
Nothing happens.
何も起きない
Nothing changes.
何も変わらない
That's her...
それが 彼女の…
制作：lastzzz 安静の云 akira アキラ
The Slasher is somewhere in this city.
この街のどこかに斬り裂き魔がいる
Every time an incident occurs, fear awakes and
spreads rumors along a heavy and stagnant night breeze.
事件が起こる度に不安に呼び覚まされた恐怖心が
漫游字幕组
http://popgo.net/bbs/
重くよどんだ夜の風に
無数の噂を巻き起こす しかし…
However...
Next Time: Uproar.